<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>OurCFB</title>
    <link href="https://bakonydraco.github.io/ourcfb/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://bakonydraco.github.io/ourcfb" />
    <updated>2022-09-15T00:06:45-07:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>bakonydraco</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://bakonydraco.github.io/ourcfb</id>

    <entry>
        <title>/r/CFB Reporting: Photos from the Clemson Furman Game</title>
        <author>
            <name>bakonydraco</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://bakonydraco.github.io/ourcfb/rcfb-reporting-photos-from-the-clemson-furman-game.html"/>
        <id>https://bakonydraco.github.io/ourcfb/rcfb-reporting-photos-from-the-clemson-furman-game.html</id>

        <updated>2022-09-15T00:06:45-07:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://bakonydraco.github.io/ourcfb/media/posts/3/DSC00670.jpg" alt="" />
                    By Josh Priddy With the spread being 45.5, it’s safe to say this one was over before it got started.
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://bakonydraco.github.io/ourcfb/media/posts/3/DSC00670.jpg" alt="" />
                <p>By Josh Priddy </p>
<p>With the spread being 45.5, it’s safe to say this one was over before it got started. Nevertheless, the final score of this game was 35-12. </p>
<p>Clemson Quarterback DJ Uiagalelei showed improvements (21/27, 231 yds in the air, 2 TD’S &amp; 1 INT), but still has a long way to go if Clemson wants to find itself with National Championship hopes at the end of the season. </p>
<p>PHOTOS:
<a href="https://photos.app.goo.gl/kA3YUGSiw1u6AHVB6">Highlights</a></p>
<p><a href="https://photos.app.goo.gl/h4RHaiHByBL9FzEv9">All Photos</a></p>
<p>Side Note:
Clemson has a long standing tradition called “The Tiger Walk” where players walk from the team busses to stadium and are greeted by fans. Rather than wearing suits like normal, all players were seen wearing matching t-shirts reading “Ella Strong.” Ella is battling a tough form of cancer, and is the sister of Defensive Tackle Bryan Bresee. It was pretty cool to see the entire team come together, and have Bryan lead the team into the stadium during this week’s Tiger Walk</p>

            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>/r/CFB Reports: FIU claws back from deficit, wins 38–37 in OT over Bryant</title>
        <author>
            <name>bakonydraco</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://bakonydraco.github.io/ourcfb/rcfb-reports-fiu-claws-back-from-deficit-wins-38-37-in-ot-over-bryant.html"/>
        <id>https://bakonydraco.github.io/ourcfb/rcfb-reports-fiu-claws-back-from-deficit-wins-38-37-in-ot-over-bryant.html</id>

        <updated>2022-09-14T23:45:58-07:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://bakonydraco.github.io/ourcfb/media/posts/2/Q_jDba9y.jpeg" alt="" />
                    FIU kicked off a new era Thursday night: new head coach, new uniforms, new culture. Whether this new era will&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://bakonydraco.github.io/ourcfb/media/posts/2/Q_jDba9y.jpeg" alt="" />
                <p>FIU kicked off a new era Thursday night: new head coach, new uniforms, new culture. Whether this new era will lead to success remains to be seen, but for now, Panther fans are celebrating their first win in a very long time.<br><br>FIU (1–0) edged by Bryant (0–1) 38–37 in OT, the team’s first win in 364 days (September 2, 2021 vs. Long Island). The Bulldogs were the dominant team throughout most of the affair and appeared destined to win the game on multiple occasions. However, the Panthers showed just enough resilience to keep in the game and ultimately prevail at the end.<br><br>The game was fairly lackluster for the first three quarters: 22 combined points, six punts, two fumble turnovers, two turnovers on downs. But Bryant held a 16–6 advantage that was seemingly insurmountable given FIU’s performance on offense to that point. FIU’s troubles on offense were compounded when graduate starting QB Gunnar Holmberg (transfer from Duke) left the game in the 3rd quarter after taking a hit to the head from Bryant junior DE Chris Eaton Jr. Eaton Jr. was ejected for targeting, but Holmberg remained out for the rest of the game, being replaced by sophomore Grayson James. FIU’s new head coach Mike MacIntyre confirmed after the game that Holmberg had a concussion.<br><br>The game’s pace picked up in the 4th, though, as FIU scored 14 unanswered points to take a 20–16 lead with 9:25 remaining. The teams then scored three touchdowns (two for Bryant, one for FIU) in just under six minutes, resulting in a 30–27 Bryant lead with 43 seconds remaining. <br><br>On the ensuing drive, FIU had to convert a 4th and 10 from their 25 yard line with 23 seconds remaining. They were bailed out by another Bryant targeting foul that kept the drive alive. FIU continued to move down the field, with the drive capped off by a game-tying 29-yard field goal as time expired.<br><br>In overtime, FIU won the coin toss and elected to defend first. Bryant scored on their first play via a 25-yard pass from sophomore QB Zevi Eckhaus to senior WR Anthony Frederick to make the score 37–30. FIU came perilously close to a 4th and 11 on their first set of downs, but a Bryant pass interference once again kept FIU going. The Panthers eventually scored on a pass from James to senior star WR Tyrese Chambers. MacIntyre then made a surprise call and elected to go for a two-point conversion. The call ended up working out as Grayson connected with sophomore WR EJ Wilson Jr. for the game-winning score.<br> <br>Both teams ended up with certain players setting themselves apart with their performance. On offense for Bryant, their two-QB system of Eckhaus and graduate Gage Moloney went a combined 29–40 for 349 yards, while senior RB Ishad Byarm led the way for the running game with 48 yards on 19 attempts. Senior LB Ryan Saddler was the team’s workhorse on defense, getting 10 tackles (3 solo), two tackles for loss, two pass breakups, and one QB hurry. <br><br>For FIU, James stepped into a tough situation mid-game but put up 207 yards on 16–31 passing, and the receiving corps was led by Chambers (8 receptions for 86 yards) and redshirt sophomore WR Kris Mitchell (3 receptions for 80 yards). Defensively, FIU had several key contributors, but sophomore DB Jamal Potts stood out with 7 tackles (5 solo), one tackle for loss, two pass breakups, and a QB hurry.<br><br>Ultimately a win is a win, especially for a team that has experienced so little in the past two seasons: FIU is now 2–18 since their upset win over Miami (FL) on November 23, 2019, and those two wins have been over FCS opponents.<br><br>But for a team seeking to move past its losing woes, a one-point win over an FCS team raises more than a few questions. The loss of Holmberg for an undetermined amount of time adds to the uncertainty for the Panthers.<br><br>Although the team ended the evening on a high note, the day’s events did begin on a somber note as the team honored Luke Knox prior to the game. Knox, who transferred from Ole Miss prior to the season, died two weeks ago. There was a moment of silence, and team captains Chambers and junior LB Donovan Manual carried out Knox’s jersey as they walked onto the field. The team also wore #16 memorial stickers (Knox’s number) on their helmet.<br><br>Next Up<br><br>FIU’s next matchup is next Saturday where they head to San Marcos, TX to face Texas State. The game kicks off at 7 PM Eastern and will be broadcast on ESPN+.<br><br>Bryant’s next matchup is also next Saturday for their home opener against Rhode Island. The game starts at 6 PM Eastern and will also be broadcast on ESPN+.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>/r/CFB Talks: Sun Belt Commissioner Keith Gill (Wed @ 10am ET) — plus YOUR CALLS on Tues night — on Twitter Spaces</title>
        <author>
            <name>bakonydraco</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://bakonydraco.github.io/ourcfb/rcfb-talks-sun-belt-commissioner-keith-gill-wed-10am-et-plus-your-calls-on-tues-night-on-twitter-spaces.html"/>
        <id>https://bakonydraco.github.io/ourcfb/rcfb-talks-sun-belt-commissioner-keith-gill-wed-10am-et-plus-your-calls-on-tues-night-on-twitter-spaces.html</id>

        <updated>2022-09-14T23:46:05-07:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://bakonydraco.github.io/ourcfb/media/posts/1/Gill.jpeg" alt="" />
                    Got our first sitting conference commissioner joining us so we wanted to share it: /r/CFB Talk 73: Your Calls, listener&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://bakonydraco.github.io/ourcfb/media/posts/1/Gill.jpeg" alt="" />
                <p>Got our first sitting conference commissioner joining us so we wanted to share it:</p>
<ul>
<li><p>/r/CFB Talk 73: <strong>Your Calls</strong>, listener call-in show (Tuesday at 10pm ET, <a href="https://twitter.com/i/spaces/1MYxNgrpREVKw?s=20">link</a>)</p>
</li>
<li><p>/r/CFB Talk 74: <strong>Keith Gill</strong>, <a href="#l/sunbelt"></a> Sun Belt Commissioner (Wednesday at 10am ET, <a href="https://twitter.com/i/spaces/1MYGNgrjlazJw?s=20">link</a>)</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p>Twitter Spaces are available on Twitter (we try to schedule them ahead), you can listen from desktop or mobile, but to participate they corral you into using the mobile app.  ¯\_(ツ)_/¯</p>
<p>⚠️ <strong>They are automatically recorded, just use the same link to listen. We also a good about getting the <a href="https://rcfb.podbean.com/">podcast format</a> up fairly quickly for those who don’t use Twitter or prefer it in podcast format.</strong> ⚠️</p>
<p>⚠️ <strong>You <em>don’t</em> need a Twitter account to listen.</strong> ⚠️</p>
<hr>
<p>#<a href="#l/media"></a> YOUR CALLS! </p>
<hr>
<p>We started Talks with taking your calls on Tuesday nights and we are continuing the Tuesday night tradition!</p>
<p>Join us live on Tuesday (9/13) @ 10pm ET for your calls!</p>
<hr>
<p>#<a href="#l/sunbelt"></a> KEITH GILL, Sun Belt Commissioner</p>
<hr>
<p>Keith Gill was named the Sun Belt Conference’s sixth commissioner on March 19, 2019, succeeding Karl Benson. The conference has grown leaps and bounds in the last decade, becoming one of the winners of recent conference realignment and then having the best football weekend in its history with earthshaking upsets on the road at Texas A&amp;M (App State), Notre Dame (Marshall), and Nebraska (Georgia Southern). We’ll be talking about the strength of the “New Sun Belt” and their regional/divisional model, their approach to realignment, the conference’s Sun Belt’s growth/rise in the CFP era, CFP expansion and its impact for the conference, and the success of the Sun Belt beyond football (baseball and softball especially, but also men’s soccer). </p>
<ul>
<li>Sun Belt Conference: <a href="https://sunbeltsports.org/staff.aspx?staff=43">Keith Gill</a></li>
<li>Twitter: <a href="https://twitter.com/SunBelt">@SunBelt</a></li>
</ul>
<p>Join us live on Wednesday (9/14) @ 10am ET for Commissioner Gill.</p>
<hr>
<p>###Recordings will be immediately available at the Twitter link <em>and</em> (after a short delay) where you get your podcasts!</p>
<hr>
<p>All of our past shows are now available via all major podcast clients: </p>
<p><a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/r-cfb-talk/id1636170090">Apple Podcast</a> | [Google Podcasts] (<a href="https://podcasts.google.com/feed/aHR0cHM6Ly9mZWVkLnBvZGJlYW4uY29tL3JDRkIvZmVlZC54bWw">https://podcasts.google.com/feed/aHR0cHM6Ly9mZWVkLnBvZGJlYW4uY29tL3JDRkIvZmVlZC54bWw</a>) | <a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/0wGYwXeg1fibmmDUvqkvuB">Spotify</a> | <a href="https://music.amazon.com/podcasts/52931701-af8d-484b-bc39-afa20d275439">Amazon Music</a> | <a href="http://tun.in/plvnF">TuneIN</a> | <a href="https://iheart.com/podcast/99743000">iHeartRadio</a> | <a href="https://rcfb.podbean.com/">etc.</a></p>
<p>Previous guests include: South Carolina HC Shane Beamer, Texas Tech HC Joey McGuire, UTSA HC Jeff Traylor, TCU AD Jeremiah Donati, Cincy AD Jon Cunningham, NDSU AD Matt Larsen, Homefield Apparel’s Connor Hitchcock, Phil Steele, Nicole Auerbach, Ross Dellenger, Jon Wilner, John Canzano, Freezing Cold Takes, and many more!</p>

            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
